alright guys welcome back and in this video I'm going to show you guys how to
好的伙伴 欢迎回来 视频我要 告诉你们 如何
convert image modes from a photo so right now all of these photos baby Bucky
从 照片转换图像模式 现在所有 这些照片 宝贝Bucky
all of these are RGB and actually 99% of the pictures you see on your computer on
所有这些都是RGB，实际上99％ 的 您在 计算机上 看到的图片
your smart phone on your tablet those are all RGB because that's what
您 在平板电脑上 的 智能手机 都是RGB 因为那是什么
computers and electronics they work with easiest they display it really easy and
与 他们合作的 电脑和电子产品 最简单的，他们显示它很容易和
crystal-clear however there are going to be times when you want to convert your
水晶般清澈 然而有了 是你想转换你的时间
image to something else for example your printer chances are that it doesn't use
图像到其他东西 ，例如你的 打印机的机会是它不 使用
RGB whenever you print out on like a picture it usually prints in 4-color
无论何时打印出来都 像 RGB 一样 它 通常以4色打印
CMYK cyan magenta yellow and K is black I don't know why they just don't use B
CMYK 青色洋红色黄色，K为黑色 我不知道为什么他们只是不使用B.
but they're going to be times where you want to take an RGB image and convert it
但他们会成为你的时代 想要拍摄 RGB图像 并进行转换
to something else so again um if you ever print something out then it's a
到别的 如此反复嗯 ，如果你 永远打印出来的东西 然后就是了
smart idea to convert it to CMYK first but just for this example I'll show you
聪明的想法首先将 其 转换 为CMYK 但只是为了这个例子，我会 告诉你
guys how to convert it to black and white now there are a couple different
伙计们如何 将它转换为黑色和 白色现在有 几个不同
ways that you can make a black-and-white image you can just take your RGB image
你可以做出黑白的方式 您可以拍摄RGB图像
and remove all the basic saturation from it and end up with a black and white
并从中 删除所有 基本饱和度 它结束了黑色和白色
image but that isn't how true black and white image that's just a an RGB that
图像， 但这 不是 多么 真实的黑色和 白色图像只是一个RGB
looks like a black and white one so if you actually want a true black and white
看起来像黑白一样，如果 你真的想要 一个真正的黑色和白色
um photo then what you can do is you can take your original photo actually this
嗯照片然后你可以做的就是你可以 把你的原始照片其实 这
is called baby and you call something called convert now convert basically
被称为宝贝，你打电话给某事 叫转换现在基本上转换
says okay what format do you want to change this to so by default this is RGB
说好的 你想要什么格式 将此更改为默认情况下这 是RGB
so if we call this nothing what happened because it's already RGB we can also do
所以，如果我们 称之为发生了什么 因为它已经是RGB 我们也可以做到
CMYK for printing but just for this example on type L now L stands for
CMYK 用于打印，但仅限于此 类型 L 上的示例现在L代表
luminance it basically means black and white they should have named it
亮度它基本上意味着黑色和 他们应该将它命名为白色
something a little bit more clear but apparently they decided that L was
更清楚的东西但是 显然他们认为 L是
best symbol for black and white so now if we take this new object which is
现在是黑白 最好的 象征 如果我们把这个新的对象 ，它是
pretty much this image of a baby now converted to a black and white file type
现在几乎是这个婴儿的形象 转换为黑白文件类型
check this out whenever you show this run main black and white now if you guys
每当你出现这个时，请检查一下 如果你们的话，现在运行主要的黑色和白色
are like alright so how do I know that this isn't just the RGB image still and I don't know they just like remove some
好像没事， 所以我怎么知道 这不仅仅是 RGB 图像 我不知道他们只是喜欢删除一些
color from it so right now keep the file open and if you go to channels you see
从它的颜色，所以现在保留文件 打开，如果你去你看到的频道
that we don't have those RGB red green blue channels anymore we just have this
我们没有那些RGB红绿色 蓝色通道我们 只是有这个
one channel just for black and white so that way we can verify that indeed it
一个通道只是为了 黑色和白色 所以 这样我们就可以确认 它
does work and well I'm not lying all right hold on just my microphone a
做工作，以及我没有说谎 所有 右边握住我的麦克风a
little bit so that was kind of boring so now since you guys had to suffer through
一点点， 所以 有点无聊 现在，因为你们不得不 通过 忍受
that I'll show you guys something really cool now pillow or pill hota
我 真的 会告诉 你们一些事情 现在 很酷的 枕头或药丸 hota
oh these gusting all right so right now we've been using bunch of functions from
哦，这些阵风现在好了 我们一直在使用一堆函数
the image class but it also has another um class that it's actually a lot cooler
图像类但它还有另一个 嗯 ，它真的很酷
in my opinion and that's image filter now this class comes with a bunch of
在我看来，这是图像过滤器 现在这个班有一堆
cool built-in on filters that you might use like blur if you ever want to blur your image if you ever want to uh do
很酷的内置在 你可能的 过滤器上 如果你想要 模糊 ，请 使用 模糊 如果你想 呵做你的形象
something like find the edges of it that's a nice little cool effect oh my
像找到它的边缘之类的东西 这是一个很好的小酷效果哦我的
that uh that was embarrassing but uh probably not even going to edit that out
那个尴尬但是呃 可能 甚至不会 编辑 出来
all right so first let me show you guys how to blur your image so do we want to
没事所以首先让我告诉你们 如何模糊图像这么做 ， 我们要
use this actually let me use Bucky actually alright let's use sister
使用这个实际 让我使用Bucky 实际上好吧让我们用妹妹
because look at this look how adorable I look in this one I am one hot piece of
因为看这个看起来 多么可爱我 看看这一个我是一个热门的一块
meat alright so sister
肉 好吧，所以姐姐
sister and just make any object I'm going to name my blurry because I'm
姐姐，只是 做任何对象我 我的名字是 模糊的，因为我
pretty much just going to blur the image so if we take sister that original image
非常简单， 只是去 模糊图像 所以，如果我们把妹妹那个原始形象
and we add a function called filter to it what this does is that allows us to pretty much pass in one of these
我们添加一个 名为filter 的 函数 它的作用是什么 让我们能够做到 其中一个很好
parameters and the parameter I want to pass in is blur so pretty much from the
参数和我想要的参数 传中在模糊这么漂亮从多
image filter class we're going to call a function called filter and it's going to
图像过滤器类我们打算调用一个 函数叫做 过滤器，它会去
blur this image so let me just show you guys real quick so blur dot show is
模糊这个图像所以让我告诉你 伙计真快，所以模糊 点秀是
pretty much the same image as before but now it is blurred pretty cool pretty
几乎 相同的 图像之前，但 现在很模糊 很漂亮
cool so as you can see um you're like okay when the heck would I want to blur image because this is just stupid it
很酷， 所以你可以 看到你是谁 好吧， 当 我想要模糊 因为这只是愚蠢的形象
like um is the same image but less quality actually if you ever um I'll
像嗯是相同的图像，但更少 质量， 如果你曾经，我会
show you guys an example and this is actually a really useful tip if you ever
告诉你们一个例子，这是 如果有的话， 其实是一个非常 有用的 提示
have an image like a flower or something and you know on those high-end cameras
有一个像花或 什么的图像 而且你知道那些高端相机
when you get that depth of field it looks like the background is kind of
当你获得那个景深时 貌似背景是怎么 样的
blurry if you ever want to add a photo filter like that then what you can do is
如果您想要添加照片，则模糊不清 过滤那样你可以做的就是
you can actually um pretty much overlay this blurry image on top of the regular
你实际上可以覆盖很多 这个模糊的图像在常规的顶部
crystal-clear image and blur it as it fades out and it'll look like kind of give you the fake effect of depth of
清澈图像和模糊， 因为它 淡出， 看起来很像 给你假的深度效果
field if you don't know what that the field is then just ignore everything I
田野， 如果你不知道那是什么 那么田野就是忽略了 我的 一切
just said because I'm not important I'll show you guys the effect later on
刚说，因为我不重要我会 告诉你们以后的效果
alright so another one that you guys might find pretty cool is detail and she
好吧， 所以另一个你们 可能会发现很酷的细节和她
let me write both of these first and what this does is it pretty much just
让我写 这些第一 都 和 它的作用非常恰到好处
gets the detail of her image it's kind of hard to explain but uh you'll see it
得到她的形象的细节它是亲切的 很难 解释， 但是你会看到它
later on sure let's uh name this one edges and the
后来肯定 让我们把这个边缘命名为
property is find edges there you go so now we already sub blur
财产是找到边缘 你去的地方现在我们已经 模糊了
so now let's go ahead and print detail see what that one does and also edges should let me clear this out alright so
所以现在让我们继续 打印 细节 看看那个人做了什么以及边缘 应该让我好吗清除了这一点， 所以
run all those make sure I didn't do anything wrong
运行所有那些确保我没有做 什么错
all right so this is blur we already saw this this is detail you
好吧所以这很模糊 我们已经看到了这个细节你
know without comparing them side by side they kind of look weird but if you look
不知道并排比较它们侧 他们看起来很奇怪， 但如果你看
at the other one then um it's pretty much like the
在另一个 然后嗯 它非常 像
opposite of blur it gets the detail and you guys can see if you compare them
与模糊相反，它获得了细节和 你们可以看看你是否 比较它们
side by side and this one obviously what it does is it finds the edges it's best
并排，这显然 是什么 它确实找到了最好的边缘
guess and it highlights them so again you probably just want to want to use
猜测，它再次突出显示它们 你 可能只是想希望 使用
this stand alone but combined with some other filters and effects they cannot
这个独立但结合 了一些 其他过滤器和效果， 他们不能
produce some pretty cool image effects so that ladies and gentlemen is image filter for some really basic built in
产生一些非常酷的图像效果 所以女士们，先生们是形象 过滤一些非常基本的 内置
filters and again the power of this actually comes when you combine it with
过滤器再次具有此功能 当你与它相结合其实来自
other stuff we're going to be taking a look at that later on but for now thank
其他 我们将采取的东西 稍后看看， 但 现在 谢谢
you guys for watching w subscribe and I'll see you guys later
你们 看 w订阅和 以后 我会看到 你们